<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyKitab Comp TE PU</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3703525445460778/6269513245</string>

    <string name="features3">\n India\'s yearly output of engineering graduates is nearly 1.5 Million but 80% of them lack necessary skill and are hence  unemployable.\n\n The industry needs skilled labor, not book worms.Pratical training and hands-on experience is the need of the day.\n\n The college syllabus introduces a subject in great detail and often it cumbersome to study all such subjects in depth .The time is right to evolve,adapt and equip yourself with tools that satisfy the demands of today and have a bright career ahead.\n </string>

    <string name="maintainence">Coming Soon!</string>

    <string name="features">&quot;Knowledge is power.Information is liberating. Education is the premise of progress, in every society, in every family.&quot; \n \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t ~ Kofi Annan</string>

    <string name="features4">\n&#8226; Mykitab consists of notes made from various reference books, thus saving you heaps of effort, energy and time which allows you to utilise that time to learn new and useful things beyond the traditional college syllabus.  \n\n &#8226; A specially designed step by step problem solving approach that MyKitab employs is exactly what you need to facilitate sound learning.\n\n &#8226; To add to this, you save plenty of data due to the app\'s low data usage.\n\n &#8226; It\'s portability allows you to learn on the go with just a touch of your finger.\n\n &#8226;You save paper by going digital. So it is literally success at your own fingertips without burning a hole in your pockets for extra tuitions.\n</string>

    <string name="terms">MyKitab respects the intellectual property rights of others and expects our users to do the same. We will respond to notices of alleged copyright infringement that comply with applicable law and are properly provided to us and will immediately remove or disable the content until further settlement.\n
\nIf you believe that your Content has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us with the following information:\n(i) a physical or electronic signature of the copyright owner or a person authorized to act on their behalf;\n(ii) identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed; \n(iii) identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;\n(iv) your contact information, including your address, telephone number, and an email address; \n(v) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and \n(vi) a statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and, under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner
\n\nWe reserve the right to remove Content alleged to be infringing without prior notice and at our sole discretion.

</string>
</resources>
